# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

#### PERSONAL PARTICULARS

Name: Peter Mgembe

Date of Birth: 01st August 2022

**Nationality:** Tanzanian

Sex: Male

Marital status: Single Phone Number: 0759867315

Email Address: peterrobsson@gmail.com

### PERSONAL PROFILE

To earn a job that utilizes my skills and experience, to succeed in an environment of growth and excellence, to work hard with full determination and dedication and to achieve personal as well as organizational goals.

And that is exactly what I'm going to do

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar, 2022 - Present Ajiriwa Network : Software Developer

I have been working tirelessly to make sure that each and every thing works as intended in the scenario of working hard

Dec, 2022 - Present Ajiriwa Network : Chief Executive Officer

Made sure that I work hard and making the best out a system that was in place for us and for everyone else apart from me

# EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

2013 - 2017 Bachelor of Business Administration : Okan University

## SKILLS

§ Microsoft Office§ PhpStorm§ C ProgrammingIntermediate

# LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

§ Kiswahili: Native / Bilingual
§ English: Full Professional

## REFEREES

Apart from my personal information mentioned in this Curriculum Vitae other information with some recommendations may be sought freely from:

#### **James Cameroon**

Dhl Supply Chain turkey 05313917352

Email: peterrobsson@gmail.com